https://www.jbhe.com/privacy

Home
About JBHE
Theodore Lamont Cross (1924-2010)
The Journal of Blacks in Higher Education
JBHE is dedicated to the conscientious investigation of the status and prospects for African Americans in higher education.
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for The Journal of Blacks in Higher Education and JBHE.com.  This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.  It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. When subscribing to an email campaign, the information submitted by you is stored on a secure MailChimp server, but they “will not, under any circumstances, steal [our] lists, contact people on [our] lists, market to people on [our] lists, sell [our] lists, or share [our] lists with any other party.”
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.  We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.  You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or contact form given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
You can unsubscribe from our email newsletter(s) at any time by clicking the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of each newsletter.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information.  When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Activity Log
This feature only records activities of a site’s registered users, and the retention duration of activity data will depend on the site’s plan and activity type.
Data Used: To deliver this functionality and record activities around site management, the following information is captured: user email address, user role, user login, user display name, WordPress.com and local user IDs, the activity to be recorded, the WordPress.com-connected site ID of the site on which the activity takes place, the site’s Jetpack version, and the timestamp of the activity. Some activities may also include the actor’s IP address (login attempts, for example) and user agent.
Activity Tracked: Login attempts/actions, post and page update and publish actions, comment/pingback submission and management actions, plugin and theme management actions, widget updates, user management actions, and the modification of other various site settings and options. Retention duration of activity data depends on the site’s plan and activity type. See the complete list of currently-recorded activities (along with retention information).
Data Synced (?): Successful and failed login attempts, which will include the actor’s IP address and user agent.
Protect
Data Used: In order to check login activity and potentially block fraudulent attempts, the following information is used: attempting user’s IP address, attempting user’s email address/username (i.e. according to the value they were attempting to use during the login process), and all IP-related HTTP headers attached to the attempting user.
Activity Tracked: Failed login attempts (these include IP address and user agent). We also set a cookie (jpp_math_pass) for 1 day to remember if/when a user has successfully completed a math captcha to prove that they’re a real human. Learn more about this cookie.
Data Synced (?): Failed login attempts, which contain the user’s IP address, attempted username or email address, and user agent information.
Sharing
Data Used: When sharing content via email (this option is only available if Akismet is active on the site), the following information is used: sharing party’s name and email address (if the user is logged in, this information will be pulled directly from their account), IP address (for spam checking), user agent (for spam checking), and email body/content. This content will be sent to Akismet (also owned by Automattic) so that a spam check can be performed. Additionally, if reCAPTCHA (by Google) is enabled by the site owner, the sharing party’s IP address will be shared with that service. You can find Google’s privacy policy here.
WordPress.com Stats
Data Used: IP address, WordPress.com user ID (if logged in), WordPress.com username (if logged in), user agent, visiting URL, referring URL, timestamp of event, browser language, country code. Important: The site owner does not have access to any of this information via this feature. For example, a site owner can see that a specific post has 285 views, but he/she cannot see which specific users/accounts viewed that post. Stats logs — containing visitor IP addresses and WordPress.com usernames (if available) — are retained by Automattic for 28 days and are used for the sole purpose of powering this feature.
Activity Tracked: Post and page views, video plays (if videos are hosted by WordPress.com), outbound link clicks, referring URLs and search engine terms, and country. When this module is enabled, Jetpack also tracks performance on each page load that includes the Javascript file used for tracking stats. This is exclusively for aggregate performance tracking across Jetpack sites in order to make sure that our plugin and code is not causing performance issues. This includes the tracking of page load times and resource loading duration (image files, Javascript files, CSS files, etc.). The site owner has the ability to force this feature to honor DNT settings of visitors. By default, DNT is currently not honored.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via phone at (570) 871-5329 or via email.
The incoming administration has voiced its support to allow athletes who were born as male but now identify as female to compete in women’s college sports. Do you agree with this proposed policy?
Yes
No
Follow @JBHEdotcom
Follow @JBHEJobs
Archives Archives
Select Month
December 2020  (148)
November 2020  (320)
October 2020  (324)
September 2020  (88)
August 2020  (86)
July 2020  (91)
June 2020  (90)
May 2020  (86)
April 2020  (83)
March 2020  (92)
February 2020  (85)
January 2020  (88)
December 2019  (92)
November 2019  (91)
October 2019  (93)
September 2019  (89)
August 2019  (93)
July 2019  (100)
June 2019  (86)
May 2019  (99)
April 2019  (97)
March 2019  (95)
February 2019  (89)
January 2019  (95)
December 2018  (92)
November 2018  (93)
October 2018  (99)
September 2018  (89)
August 2018  (97)
July 2018  (97)
June 2018  (92)
May 2018  (97)
April 2018  (96)
March 2018  (94)
February 2018  (89)
January 2018  (102)
December 2017  (93)
November 2017  (90)
October 2017  (89)
September 2017  (94)
August 2017  (97)
July 2017  (93)
June 2017  (95)
May 2017  (102)
April 2017  (87)
March 2017  (100)
February 2017  (86)
January 2017  (94)
December 2016  (96)
November 2016  (94)
October 2016  (95)
September 2016  (97)
August 2016  (103)
July 2016  (95)
June 2016  (97)
May 2016  (98)
April 2016  (94)
March 2016  (97)
February 2016  (96)
January 2016  (95)
December 2015  (105)
November 2015  (95)
October 2015  (99)
September 2015  (96)
August 2015  (94)
July 2015  (102)
June 2015  (97)
May 2015  (98)
April 2015  (101)
March 2015  (106)
February 2015  (89)
January 2015  (91)
December 2014  (98)
November 2014  (91)
October 2014  (104)
September 2014  (106)
August 2014  (92)
July 2014  (100)
June 2014  (100)
May 2014  (99)
April 2014  (99)
March 2014  (93)
February 2014  (96)
January 2014  (112)
December 2013  (112)
November 2013  (98)
October 2013  (92)
September 2013  (110)
August 2013  (91)
July 2013  (98)
June 2013  (91)
May 2013  (126)
April 2013  (91)
March 2013  (121)
February 2013  (95)
January 2013  (89)
December 2012  (93)
November 2012  (116)
October 2012  (106)
September 2012  (99)
August 2012  (95)
July 2012  (88)
June 2012  (107)
May 2012  (116)
April 2012  (102)
March 2012  (114)
February 2012  (96)
January 2012  (88)
December 2011  (96)
November 2011  (89)
October 2011  (101)
September 2011  (90)
August 2011  (60)
July 2011  (2)
JBHE Jobs
University of Hartford — Tenure Track Associate Professor of PianoColgate University — ITS Technology Support SpecialistLoras College — Vice President for Marketing and Strategic CommunicationUniversity of Denver — Assistant Professor of the Practice in AccountancyHope College — Assistant Professor, Social WorkYork University — Black-identified Professorial stream appointment, Theatre, Theatre History and DramaturgyYork University — Black-identified Assistant / Associate or Full Professor, Osgoode Hall Law SchoolYork University — Black-identified Professorial stream appointment in Computer ScienceYork University — Black-identified professorial stream appointment in Film ProductionYork University — Black-identified Professorial stream position in Biology, Astronomy, Astrophysics, Mathematics, StatisticsThe Pennsylvania State University — Head, Department of Mechanical EngineeringThe University of Texas at San Antonio — Dean, College of Education & Human DevelopmentSouthern Connecticut State University — Dean of the School of BusinessUniversity of Maryland, Baltimore County — Open Rank, Tenured / Tenure-Track Faculty Position in Computer ScienceReynolds Community College — Vice President, Organizational Development and Human Resources / Chief Diversity Officer #FA420Ball State University — Assistant Professor of Educational PsychologyThe University of Alabama at Birmingham — Non-Tenure Earning Assistant Professor (Teaching Faculty), Department of BiologyUniversity of Massachusetts Amherst — Assistant Dean of Inclusion and Engagement, Graduate SchoolUniversity of Pennsylvania
— Associate Professor, Clinician Educator, Adolescent MedicineUniversity of Pennsylvania
— Associate Professor, Academic Clinician, Adolescent Medicine
The Journal of Blacks in Higher Education © 2020. All rights reserved. | Privacy Policy | p: (570) 392-6797 | e: contact@jbhe.com
Follow @JBHEdotcom
